qtel.qa 2010-05-22

# Privacy Statement

**Information about our Web site**

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in our activities. Qtel is based in Qatar. Our principal activity is Telecommunication. Our privacy policy covers the Web Site. Our legal disclaimer above is applicable for your use of the Web Site, and is linked with this Privacy policy. By viewing the pages of this Web Site, you do acknowledge that you did read and accept our disclaimer and Privacy policy. If you do not want to accept the legal disclaimer and/or the privacy policy, you should leave the Web Site.   
The owner of the Web Site is Qtel. Our Head Office is situated at West Bay, PO Box 217, Doha, Qatar. 

**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. Your personal data are requested only if you want to access online services (e.g. check your email). We do not sell or provide any third party with any of the data you disclosed.   
If you are just surfing and reading information on the Web Site, as any other web site we do collect and store the following anonymous information about your visit: 

* the IP address of your machine when you were visiting the Web Site  

* the operating system and the browser your computer uses  

* any search engine you were using before arriving to the Web Site  

* the date and time of your visit   

* the URLs of the pages you visit on the Web Site 

We only use these anonymous information for statistical reasons and we will not give these anonymous information to any third party. We may keep more extensive information if we are concerned, for example, about security issues (attack against the Web Site). If necessary, or following a request of the relevant public authority, we may then keep and give to the relevant authority additional information within the legal framework of the law of Qatar.   
If you give us more information, like your email address if you contact Qtel, we will only use this information for the purpose of the service or information you requested from Qtel.   
If you log in to Messenger express trough the Web Site, Qtel will not keep any information concerning the way you use this service that is governed by the specific terms and conditions you accepted before receiving your email address. 

**The services and links of our Web site**

Our Web site does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. 

**Automatic Collection of Information**

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our survey services. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. 

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us. 

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice**

We do not disclose your personal data to any other individual or organization. 

**Privacy Support**

If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact us at [info@Qtel.com.qa](mailto:%20info@Qtel.com.qa)

**Change of this policy**

Qtel reserves the right to change, adapt, adjust this Privacy policy on the Web Site without any prior notification. You aknowledge and agree that this Policy may change from time to time and you realise that the latest version is applicable when you visit the Web Site.
